(upbeat rock music)
♪ She was more like a beauty
queen from a movie scene ♪
♪ I said don't mind, but what
do you mean, I am the one ♪
♪ Who will dance on the
floor in the round ♪
♪ She said I am the one ♪
♪ Who will dance on the
floor in the round ♪
♪ She told me her name was Billie Jean ♪
♪ As she caused a scene ♪
♪ Then every head turned with eyes ♪
♪ That dreamed of being the one ♪
♪ Who will dance on the
floor in the round ♪
♪ People always told me be
careful of what you do ♪
♪ And don't go around
breaking young girls' hearts ♪
♪ Hee ♪
♪ And mother always told me
be careful of who you love ♪
♪ And be careful of what you do ♪
♪ 'Cause the lie becomes the truth, hey ♪
♪ Billie Jean is not my lover ♪
♪ She's just a girl who
claims that I am the one ♪
♪ Oh babe ♪
♪ But the kid is not my son ♪
♪ Woo ♪
♪ She says I am the one ♪
♪ But the kid is not my son ♪
♪ Hee, hee, hee ♪
♪ For 40 days and 40 nights ♪
♪ The law was on her side ♪
♪ But who can stand when she's in demand ♪
♪ Her schemes and plans ♪
♪ 'Cause we danced on
the floor in the round ♪
♪ So take my strong advice ♪
♪ Just remember to always think twice ♪
♪ Don't think twice, do think twice ♪
♪ She told my baby we'd
danced 'til three ♪
♪ Then she looked at me ♪
♪ Then showed a photo my baby
cried his eyes were like mine ♪
♪ 'Cause we danced on the
floor in the round, baby ♪
♪ Hee, hee, hee ♪
♪ People always told me be
careful of what you do ♪
♪ And don't go around
breaking young girls' hearts ♪
♪ Don't break no hearts ♪
♪ She came and stood right by me ♪
♪ Just the smell of sweet perfume ♪
♪ This happened much too soon ♪
♪ She called me to her room, hey ♪
♪ Billie Jean is not my lover, woo ♪
♪ She's just a girl who
claims that I am the one ♪
♪ But the kid is not my son ♪
♪ Billie Jean is not my lover ♪
♪ She's just a girl who
claims that I am the one ♪
♪ But the kid is not my son ♪
♪ No, no ♪
♪ She says I am the one,
but the kid is not my son ♪
♪ She, hee, hee ♪
♪ Hee ♪
(upbeat rock music continues)
♪ She says I am the one,
but the kid is not my son ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Woo ♪
♪ Billie Jean is not my lover ♪
♪ She's just a girl who
claims that I am the one ♪
♪ No it can't be me, babe ♪
♪ But the kid is not my son ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ She says I am the one,
but the kid is not my son ♪
♪ No, no, no ♪
♪ She says I am the one ♪
♪ You know what you did ♪
♪ She says he is my son ♪
♪ Breaking my heart, babe ♪
♪ She says I am the one ♪
♪ Billie Jean is not my lover ♪
♪ Don't Billie Jean ♪
♪ Billie Jean ♪